Manoj Madhur

UX Designer

UX and UI designer with 6+ years of experience and proven skills in usability testing, wireframing, visual design and prototyping. Received **90%** positive customer feedback and an increase in UX dependency by **20%** over the years of experience. Well versed in designing products and services for Human Resources, Healthcare and Manufacturing Industries as well.

EXPERIENCE

Accenture - UX Designer

June 2021 - August 2022

Strategy Assessment for Classes (Class based Assessment in APM for SAP)

Users: Reliability Engineer

- Conducted research on RCM (Reliability Centered Maintenance) application to implement similar concepts in class based assessment
- Aligning all components, layouts and design structures according UI5
- S/4 data migration and assistance in Foundation Database
- Cross app navigation designing and support for primary function i.e. Recommendation
- Standalone Recommendation creation with consolidated results in Hierarchy
- Creating life like mockups for seamless experience with real time data gathered from S/4
- Frequent design reviews and testing to make the developed version close to proposed design

Phenom - UI Designer

September 2018 - June 2021

Chatbot (Career Site Bot and Management Platform)

Users: Candidates, Employees, Recruiters, Annotators and Content Managers

- Design user interface with prototype following the company's brand identity as well as feasibility of customer customisation
- Frequent observation of user behavior from Fullstory to improve product experience
- Continuous product enhancements as per top competitor updates to stay on top of the market
- A/B testing of features for better decision making process in terms of usability
- FAQ Creation and Management implementation for all the personas
- Bot flow personalisation for scenarios such as Explore Jobs, FAQ and Apply

QA Hub (Automation and Accessibility Testing Tool)

Users: QA testers, Implementation team and SI Partners

- Dedicated brainstorming sessions on creating a first in class Automation Testing tool applicable for all Phenom products
- Iterative process of frequent testing with real data to resolve issues before release
- Analytics and Reports Management role based access design for leadership
- Manual Testing research and ideation created to log information and improve tool to increase the overall percentage of Automation Testing
- Design Technical Configuration Management in the tool for Administrators

Implementation (Career Site)

Users: Job Seekers

- Design dev ready interface with the use of internal Phenom templates
- Branding and visual representation of Customers
- Asset creation and management

Cognizant Technology Solutions - UI Designer

February 2016 - April 2018

Aetna Navigator (Health Insurance)

Users: Healthcare Seekers and Providers

- Responsive Web Design for Desktop and Mobile as per new brand guidelines by Aetna
- Proposing concepts for better functionality in existing web pages for better usability
- Design client demo with prototype like real time application to receive potential enhancement requests

3M (Industrial Management Platform according to SAP Fiori)

Users: Administrators and Floor Managers

- Responsive Web Design for Desktop, Tablet and Mobile as per SAP Fiori Guidelines
- Creation of architecture for role based access for Product Management and Inventory
- Design framework for Mitigation plan and inventory logging

SKILLS

User Experience Design | User Interface Design | Information Architecture | User Testing | Usability Testing | Competitor Analysis | Responsive Web Design | Branding

TOOLS

- Adobe Suite
- Sketch
- Figma
- Axure

CERTIFICATION

UX Jumpstart - ImagineXP

Riverfront by the Museum (Landscape Architecture) — Architecture and Design Foundation India

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Group Lead — ARPF (Animal Rehabilitation and Protection Front) 2011 - 2012

Volunteer for Hyderabad Zoo Corps — UN COP 11 (United Nation Conference of Parties 11)
October 2012

QUALIFICATION

Master of Science in Interaction and Experience Design — University of Limerick, Limerick, Ireland 2022 - 2023

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Applied Arts — Osmania University, Hyderabad, India 2010 - 2015

10th Grade — Kendriya Vidyalaya, Chandigarh, India 2010